[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "வாழ்வியல்",
    "answers": ["வாழ்வியல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "பரிமாற்றம்",
    "answers": ["பரிமாற்றம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "குற்றச்சாட்டு",
    "answers": ["குற்றச்சாட்டு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "படகோட்டம்",
    "answers": ["படகோட்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "கொழுப்புச்சத்து",
    "answers": ["கொழுப்புச்சத்து"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "தாவரவியல்",
    "answers": ["தாவரவியல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "சோதனைக்குழாய்",
    "answers": ["சோதனைக்குழாய்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "வெற்றியாளர்",
    "answers": ["வெற்றியாளர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "சறுக்குமரம்",
    "answers": ["சறுக்குமரம்", "சறுக்கு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "பந்து",
    "answers": ["பந்து", "கைப்பந்து"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "பட்டம்",
    "answers": ["பட்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "ஏணிப்படி",
    "answers": ["ஏணிப்படி", "ஏணி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "குச்சி",
    "answers": ["குச்சி", "கழி", "கம்பு", "கோல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "மணல்",
    "answers": ["மணல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "பாய்",
    "answers": ["பாய்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "தொப்பி",
    "answers": ["தொப்பி", "குல்லா"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "மிதவை",
    "answers": ["மிதவை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "பலகை",
    "answers": ["பலகை", "மரப்பலகை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "மலைப்பகுதி",
    "answers": ["மலைப்பகுதி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "அருவருப்பு",
    "answers": ["அருவருப்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "பன்னிரண்டு",
    "answers": ["பன்னிரண்டு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "தேரோட்டம்",
    "answers": ["தேரோட்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "கழிவுநீர்",
    "answers": ["கழிவுநீர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "எழுதுகோல்",
    "answers": ["எழுதுகோல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "நன்னடத்தை",
    "answers": ["நன்னடத்தை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "பொழுதுபோக்கு",
    "answers": ["பொழுதுபோக்கு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "தலையணை",
    "answers": ["தலையணை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "வாரந்தோறும்",
    "answers": ["வாரந்தோறும்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "இளவரசர்",
    "answers": ["இளவரசர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "உருளைக்கிழங்கு",
    "answers": ["உருளைக்கிழங்கு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "அளவுகோல்",
    "answers": ["அளவுகோல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "உண்ணாவிரதம்",
    "answers": ["உண்ணாவிரதம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "வன்முறை",
    "answers": ["வன்முறை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "கண்டனம்",
    "answers": ["கண்டனம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
